[
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Andes mountain range",
    "answers": ["CL", "AR", "EC", "PE", "BO", "CO", "VE"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Himalayas mountain range",
    "answers": ["IN", "NP", "CN", "PK", "BT", "AF"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Rocky Mountains",
    "answers": ["US", "CA"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Alps mountain range",
    "answers": ["FR", "IT", "CH", "AT", "DE", "SI", "LI", "MC"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Amazon River",
    "answers": ["BR", "PE", "CO", "EC", "VE", "GY", "BO"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Nile River",
    "answers": [
      "EG",
      "SD",
      "ET",
      "UG",
      "KE",
      "TZ",
      "RW",
      "BI",
      "CD",
      "SS",
      "SD"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Mississippi River",
    "answers": ["US"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Yangtze River",
    "answers": ["CN"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Danube River",
    "answers": ["DE", "AT", "SK", "HU", "HR", "RS", "RO", "BG", "MD", "UA"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Ganges River",
    "answers": ["IN", "BD"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Caucasus Mountains",
    "answers": ["RU", "GE", "AM", "AZ"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Great Dividing Range",
    "answers": ["AU"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Volga River",
    "answers": ["RU"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Rhine River",
    "answers": ["DE", "CH", "FR", "NL", "LI", "AT"]
  },
  {
    "language": "English",
    "answers": [
      "AG",
      "AU",
      "BS",
      "BB",
      "BZ",
      "BW",
      "CM",
      "CA",
      "KI",
      "CY",
      "DM",
      "FJ",
      "GM",
      "GH",
      "GD",
      "GY",
      "IN",
      "IE",
      "JM",
      "KE",
      "LS",
      "LR",
      "MW",
      "MY",
      "MT",
      "MH",
      "MU",
      "FM",
      "MZ",
      "NA",
      "NR",
      "NZ",
      "NG",
      "PK",
      "PW",
      "PG",
      "PH",
      "RW",
      "KN",
      "LC",
      "VC",
      "WS",
      "SC",
      "SL",
      "SG",
      "SB",
      "ZA",
      "SS",
      "SD",
      "SZ",
      "TZ",
      "TO",
      "TT",
      "TV",
      "UG",
      "GB",
      "US",
      "VU",
      "ZM",
      "ZW"
    ],
    "question": "Has English as an official language"
  },
  {
    "language": "French",
    "answers": [
      "BE",
      "BJ",
      "BF",
      "BI",
      "CM",
      "CA",
      "CF",
      "TD",
      "KM",
      "CG",
      "CD",
      "CI",
      "DJ",
      "GA",
      "GN",
      "GQ",
      "HT",
      "LU",
      "MG",
      "ML",
      "MC",
      "NE",
      "RW",
      "SN",
      "SC",
      "CH",
      "TG",
      "VU",
      "FR"
    ],
    "question": "Has French as an official language"
  },
  {
    "language": "German",
    "answers": ["DE", "AT", "CH", "LI", "LU", "BE"],
    "question": "Has German as an official language"
  },
  {
    "language": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "AR",
      "BO",
      "CL",
      "CO",
      "CR",
      "CU",
      "DO",
      "EC",
      "SV",
      "GQ",
      "GT",
      "HN",
      "MX",
      "NI",
      "PA",
      "PY",
      "PE",
      "PH",
      "ES",
      "UY",
      "VE"
    ],
    "question": "Has Spanish as an official language"
  },
  {
    "language": "Portuguese",
    "answers": ["AO", "BR", "CV", "GW", "MZ", "PT", "ST", "TL"],
    "question": "Has Portuguese as an official language"
  },
  {
    "language": "Russian",
    "answers": ["BY", "KZ", "KG", "RU", "TJ", "TM", "UZ"],
    "question": "Has Russian as an official language"
  },
  {
    "language": "Persian",
    "answers": ["IR", "AF", "TJ"],
    "question": "Has Persian as an official language"
  },
  {
    "language": "Arabic",
    "answers": [
      "AE",
      "DZ",
      "BH",
      "DJ",
      "EG",
      "IQ",
      "JO",
      "KW",
      "LB",
      "LY",
      "MA",
      "MR",
      "OM",
      "PS",
      "QA",
      "SA",
      "SD",
      "SY",
      "TN",
      "YE"
    ],
    "question": "Has Arabic as an official language"
  },
  {
    "language": "Swahili",
    "answers": ["CD", "KE", "RW", "TZ", "UG"],
    "question": "Has Swahili as an official language"
  },
  {
    "language": "Malay",
    "answers": ["BN", "ID", "MY", "SG"],
    "question": "Has Malay as an official language"
  },
  {
    "language": "Italian",
    "answers": ["IT", "SM", "VA", "CH"],
    "question": "Has Italian as an official language"
  }
]
